Your form pulls up Google Maps to make sure that the address for the shipping is accurate,
so it doesn't ask the person a bunch of times to confirm.
And then since there's a site-wide sale going on for 15% off, it automatically shows up
in here.
And then it's just already populated, but with this little X button so that if the customer
happened to have a coupon code for their birthday or something else, they could clear
that out and then use a different code instead.
But we're going to just purchase it as is.
As soon as this pops up, it sends the first point of contact to the new owner of your
art.
It's a receipt that comes straight from Stripe, but it's nicely designed with the color palette
from your brand and a logo.